roundpulse.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy & Disclaimer | Round Pulse

At Round Pulse, we appreciate your privacy and make sure that your personal information remains private. If there is any personal information that you provide us through our website, we take care of it and make sure that no one has access to it in any case or condition. We encourage our readers to go through our website in detail and let us know about any bugs that they can find. Our support team is always available to assist our readers about any privacy policy issues. We also expect our readers to respect the privacy of other readers that may come into their interaction through comments or any parts of our website though we cannot guarantee about the information that you give away to anyone directly.

## Do We Collect Your Personal Information?

As per our privacy policy, we don’t collect any kind of personal information of our readers without their intention. The only way will collect and store your personal information is through contact form or the subscription option at our website, other than that, there is no way through which we ever collect your personal information.

advertisement

## How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

The reason why we collect your personal information is stated when we ask you to provide any such information. If you have provided your personal information to email subscription then we will use that information just to send you weekly, monthly or daily newsletter. The personal information that you submit while adding a post from your site will be visible below your post. We may take a look at your personal information when you comment on our blog but that is for inception purpose only, we never use that information anywhere at any place or time.

## Who has Access to My Personal Information?

Only the site administrator is given access to your personal information. The private information shared by you can only be viewed and accessed by site administrator and no one else. However, if you are sharing your personal information openly at our site (we forbid all users to do so), the information can be seen, and accessed and used by anyone and Round Pulse has no control over it.  
At Round Pulse, we appreciate our readers and users to use our site for their own benefit. Once you are at our website, you can do anything that has been made possible and available to the readers. However, we forbid our users to communicate with each other as it may bring upon an unexpected situation on you. We also forbid you to share your personal information publicly as it can be used by anyone for any purpose and Round Pulse will have nothing to do with it.

We encourage our readers to interact with each other only through comments section and make sure you stay on topic, use proper language, talk about the issue and don’t indulge in any inappropriate or unethical activity on our website.

Our posts, images, videos and any other information published on our website is our sole property. Use of this information without our authorization is prohibited. We strongly encourage you to use all the information for personal use and not use it for any commercial purpose. We may issue a lawsuit against you if you are found guilty of infringement.

Lastly, we hope that all our readers, user and fans will keep the above provided information in their mind while using our website. We are dedicated to provide you with latest information that can prove to be helpful for your daily life.

**[Google](http://www.roundpulse.com/category/google-2) Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the [Internet](http://www.roundpulse.com/tag/internet). DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content [network](http://www.roundpulse.com/tag/network) privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacyads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

advertisement
